http://dsat.ca/policy-and-disclaimer/

Policy and Disclaimer
Homepage
Policy and Disclaimer
This website reports items of interest relating to Down syndrome. It does not promote or recommend any therapy treatment, political position, or religious view. We wish to bring together those interested in Down syndrome and attempt to create an optimistic outlook and attitude.
Privacy Policy
DSAT respects the privacy of all of its users and is committed to protecting such privacy in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy explains DSAT’s treatment of your personally identifiable information collected in connection with your activities on our website and all services made available on the DSAT Site.
We urge you to read this Privacy Policy carefully and to check back periodically as this Privacy Policy may change form time to time. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies or websites that are not owned or controlled by DSAT.
Information Collected
“Personal Information” is personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, birth date and gender. Personal Information is collected by us when you choose to provide it to us when purchasing products or filling in forms such as when you choose to become a member. In addition, if you choose to contact our office, we may keep a record of that correspondence so that we may fully address the subject matter.
Disclosure of Personal Information
We will not sell or rent your Personal Information to anyone.
Links to Other Sites
The DSAT site contains links to other websites and services. While we try to link only to sites and services that share our high standards and respect for privacy, please understand that we are not responsible for the content of, or the privacy practices employed by, other companies or websites.
